<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nsec-2021 Badge on AlrikRr&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://AlrikRr.github.io/posts/write-up/nsec-2021/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nsec-2021 Badge on AlrikRr&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://AlrikRr.github.io/posts/write-up/nsec-2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>Flag #9 - Tom&#39;s Hut part2</title>
      <link>https://AlrikRr.github.io/posts/write-up/nsec-2021/9-flag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AlrikRr.github.io/posts/write-up/nsec-2021/9-flag/</guid>
      <description>If you want to fully understand this post I can only recommand you to read the previous one (Flag 8 part1)
RE102 Reverse Like the previous one, the architecture is Xtensa, but this time I already have the right module for Ghidra !
Using Ghidra I&amp;rsquo;m doing the import and the analysis of the binary.
App Main The app_main function is very similar to RE101, so this time let&amp;rsquo;s jump on the verify function !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag #8 - Tom&#39;s Hut part1</title>
      <link>https://AlrikRr.github.io/posts/write-up/nsec-2021/8-flag/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AlrikRr.github.io/posts/write-up/nsec-2021/8-flag/</guid>
      <description>The next 2 Flags are binary reverse, I was very very rusty on this one &amp;hellip;
Wi-Fi Join So, this challenge is accessible from Tom&amp;rsquo;s Hut after you have joined a Wi-Fi network !
To join a Wi-Fi network, you need to access the serial port using screen (check Chall 7 !) and use the following command:
You should receive an IP, you can now go to Tom&amp;rsquo;s Hut and see the following message !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag #7 - Reboot</title>
      <link>https://AlrikRr.github.io/posts/write-up/nsec-2021/7-flag/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AlrikRr.github.io/posts/write-up/nsec-2021/7-flag/</guid>
      <description>I was also lucky on this one.
tty CLI After connecting to the device using the serial port with the screen command:
sudo screen /dev/ttyUSB0 115200 If you can´t see your ttyUSB, try using dmesg after connecting the badge on your computer.
And also check your /dev/ folder
Reboot ! As you can see, behind the badge, there is a reboot button, and I keep pressing it by mistake!
However, after looking at the terminal, I saw the full message and a small help menu before the shell!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag #5 - Punk Down</title>
      <link>https://AlrikRr.github.io/posts/write-up/nsec-2021/5-flag/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AlrikRr.github.io/posts/write-up/nsec-2021/5-flag/</guid>
      <description>Okay for this one I don&amp;rsquo;t have the reference but I managed to found it by accident ! It&amp;rsquo;s actually the second one I found during my journey.
Punk Guy I was playing around the place and speak to this Punk Guy right here
During the conversation, I found the flag by accident by pressing the Down Button Flag 5 The flag is FLAG-KLJV490uhkEJF28</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag #1 - Welcome</title>
      <link>https://AlrikRr.github.io/posts/write-up/nsec-2021/1-flag/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AlrikRr.github.io/posts/write-up/nsec-2021/1-flag/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone ! It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since my last post but I&amp;rsquo;m still alive no worries 😁
Today I&amp;rsquo;m gonna post some write-up for the NorthSec 2021 Badge CTF ! I purchase the badge last year and din&amp;rsquo;t have time to play with it so here I am !
It&amp;rsquo;s actually my first CTF Badge and I hope im going to fine all the flags !
Device Here is a full spec of the nsec badge : available here</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
